http://www.a1scrubs.com/privacypolicy

new customer?
Please allow 7-10 business days for store credit to be applied to your account. Order history will be shown as soon as your initial order ships.
shop by brand top brand nursing scrubsADCAnywearBarco OneBarco WellnessCarharttCherokee MedicalCherokee WorkwearDickiesElleFundamentalspremium quality uniformsGrey's AnatomyGreys Anatomy ActiveGreys Anatomy EdgeGreys Anatomy ImpactGreys Anatomy SignatureHeartSoulJockey ScrubsLandauMc2Med Couturedesigner medical APPARELMetaMotion By BarcoReebokRoth WearSkechersSmittenTooniformsUrbaneWhite Swan BrandsWonderWinkNEW UNIFORMS AND SCRUBSGIFTCARDSLANDAU FABRICMed Couture AccentsMed Couture BoutiqueMed Couture EnergyMed Couture TouchRoth WearScrub ZoneTherafirmTop Men's Medical Scrubswomen'smen'sAntiMicrobialPPENEWdealsGROUPshelp/returns A1 Scrubs, Inc.
A1Scrubs
21310 Castlerock Ln
Gretna, NE 68028
(not a store location)
Serving the medical community with unbeatable customer service since 1997.
Customer Service
Happy to help Monday-Thursday 9 am 4 pm ct. Speak to a live representative by phone or by live chat below.
Toll free: 866-217-2782
Fax order line: 866-217-2783
mail@a1scrubs.com
or use our online form
Join A1 Scrubs Club
Be the first to know about new styles, special offers and members only coupons. Plus, get a special 20% OFF coupon for joining. This is an optional, free service - you may opt out anytime. (coupon excludes ScrubZone and already marked down items)
Join The Club
Return/Exchange
To return or exchange your order within 30 days of receipt, us our form below.
return/exchange form
A1Scrubs Privacy Policy
We take the privacy of your personal information seriously. This Internet Privacy Policy describes the measures we take to help ensure the security of information collected through our Web sites.
How Personal Information is Collected and Used
We only collects personal information that you voluntarily submit through our Web sites. This may include information such as your name, street and e-mail addresses, and telephone number. We do not automatically collect personal information without your knowledge.
Uses of Personal Information
When you submit personal information to us, you will be asked to decide how we may use your information. Unless we specifically tell you otherwise before you submit personal information, we will only use it to:
Respond to your questions or comments
Better understand your purchasing habits and needs
Help us understand how we can improve our products, services, and Web site
Inform you about special promotions
Contact you to ask for your opinion or willingness to participate in certain events
Limiting the Use of Your Information
If you submit personal information to us, you have two options:
You may choose to allow us to use the personal information for any of the purposes described under the "Uses of Personal Information" section of our Privacy Policy. This is called the "Opt-In" choice.
You may choose to restrict our use of your information to a specific application, such as answering your question about a product. This is called the "Opt-Out" choice.
These options give you the opportunity to control the usage of your personal information by "opting out" of our systems.
Use of Cookies
To improve your visit to our sites, we may use "cookies" to obtain non-personal information (cookies are text information files that your browser places on your computer when you visit a Web site). We may aggregate this data to analyze the viewing habits of our site visitors, but it will not be associated with any personally identifiable data.
Sharing Your Personal Information With Others
We will not use or share your personal information in ways unrelated to the uses described above unless we provide you with prior notice and give you an opportunity to change your usage preferences. Unless you give us prior consent, we will not trade, sell, or share your personal information with any person or entity other than A1Scrubs, our affiliates and representatives, unless required by law or as disclosed to you before the information is collected. For certain promotions or product requests, we may share your information with an outside company for the sole purpose of fulfilling your order. These companies are carefully selected by us and also take the protection of your personal information seriously.
Access to Your Information
To modify your personal information, contact us . We will make every effort to respond to your requests in a timely manner.If you have already submitted personal information to A1Scrubs.com, you may opt-out of the company's future use of that information.
Security of Your Information
The security of your personal information is very important to us. We use appropriate technical and managerial procedures to protect your personal information and prevent its disclosure outside of us. Only those authorized by us will be granted access to your personal information.In addition to careful consideration about what information you share and who you share it with, we recommend that everyone develop good security habits. These include protecting and regularly changing your password, using computer virus protection, logging off when you finish using your computer, and considering the use of file or email encryption programs.
E-mail Preferences
A1Scrubs offers you the opportunity to choose whether or not you prefer to receive marketing materials via e-mail. You may update this preference at any time. Please allow us sufficient time to process your change of preference.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
We may amend this Internet Privacy Policy from time to time. Please check back for updates.
© 2020 Powered by Sellers Commerce
